pppst.com 2019-12-08

# Pete's Place Privacy Policy

## Privacy & Cookie Policy

[pppst.com](https://www.pppst.com/index.html) does not collect information on visitors to its Website.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.

  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to our website. These ads are provided by [Google](http://www.google.com/) via the [Google AdSense program](http://www.google.com/adsense). pppst.com does not select the ads or control the content of ads provided by Google via the Google AdSense program.

  * Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and/or other sites on the Internet.

  * Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest based advertising by visiting Google’s [Ads Personalization Settings](https://adssettings.google.com/).

  * Alternately, users can opt out of Google’s use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).

  * To learn more about how Google uses information from pppst.com, see [“How Google Uses Information from Sites or Apps That Use Our Services”](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites) and visit the Google [Privacy & Terms](https://policies.google.com/) site. 

**pppst.com uses a third party technology called Ezoic.** To learn more about how Ezoic collects and uses information—or to change your privacy consent settings for Ezoic services on this website—visit the [Ezoic Service Privacy Policy](https://g.ezoic.net/privacy/pppst.com) for pppst.com.

## Privacy Policy Regarding Children

Pppst does not:

Collect online contact information from a child under 13.   If Pppst ever does collect such information, it will gain prior verifiable parental consent or direct parental notification of the nature and intended use of this information, which shall include an opportunity for the parent to prevent use of the information and participation in the activity.   Where prior parental consent is not obtained, online contact information shall only be used to directly respond to the child's request and shall not be used to re-contact the child for other purposes. Emails from children are not saved after responding to their questions.

Pppst does not:

Collect personally identifiable offline contact information from children under 13 without prior verifiable parental consent.

Pppst does not:

Distribute to third parties any Personally Identifiable Information collected from a child under 13 without prior verifiable parental consent.

Give the ability to children under 13 to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior verifiable parental consent, and will make best efforts to prohibit a child from posting any contact information.

Entice a child under 13 by the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity, to divulge more information than is needed to participate in such activity.

If pppst ever requests personally identifiable information, we will also place prominent notice where personally identifiable information is collected, requesting the child to ask a parent for permission to answer the questions.

## Privacy Policy Regarding Adults

Pppst does not:

Collect personally identifiable information. If it does begin collecting such information, prior consent will be obtained from the users of the site, options will be provided to not provide such information, and the uses of the information will be specified.   If information will be divulged to third parties, users will be notified prior to collecting the information.
